

Ferencz Balog

Junior Web Developer

Passion, Challenge-seeker, Professional Improvement, are the those three expressions that describes me.

In 2016 I accepted a job at a teather because of the passion of backstage activities and achiveing new skills, three years later I accepted the challenge to run a small enterprise alone from the passion of cycling and few months later I've started to improve my abilities as Sound Engineer and Web Developer.

Professional Skills

Δ	ď	va	n	r	Δ	Ч
$\boldsymbol{-}$	ч	v u		·	u	ч

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, WordPress, JSON

Intermediate

JavaScript, API fetch, Relational Databases

Beginner

NodeJs, ReactJs

Still Learning

Java

Work Experience

■ balogferencz.artist@gmail.com

4 +40 752 813 860

Cluj-Napoca, Cluj, RO

• FerenczBalog

ferenczbalog.github.io

in ferenczbalog

Spoken languages (CEFR scale)

C2: Hungarian, Romanian C1: English

PUCK Puppet Theatre, Cluj-Napoca, 01.2017 - 08.2023 Stage Technician

Earned soft skills:

Working on Pressure, Time Management, Atention to details, Communication, Engagement, Teamwork, Problem Solving

Balog I. Ferencz PFA, Cluj-Napoca, 07.2019 - present Founder, Food-Delivery, Stage Technician

Earned soft skills:

Time Management, Attention to details, Communication, Engagement, Problem Solving, Working with clients

Education

PLATFORMAIT.ro, 08.2020 - 08.2022

Hard skills:

Basics of HTML, CSS and JavaScript

TEACHBIT.ro, 08.2022 - present

Hard skills:

Advenced of HTML, CSS and JavaScript

Software knowledge

Visual Studio Code github Adobe Dreamweaver Sourcetree Inkscape Canva Figma Adobe Photoshop GIMP

Passions

Cycling Photography Reading Programming Free-writting

My Projects

Mylifedash, 01.2023 - present

Hard skills:

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, API fetch

Because we live in a fast-paced world, I am working on a webpage that can help everyone manage their life. The first version of the website contains only a weather function, providing a three-day forecast fetching an API data. I wrote it using HTML and JS, and styled it with CSS.

RiderBox, 03.2023 - present

Hard skills:

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JavaScript modules, OOP, JSON

While working in the theatre as stage technician I missed a platform that can store the riders of current performances, so I created one. The first version was made using only HTML and CSS, the actual version is based on Javascript modules and Bootstrap.

The first web-portfolio, 2021

Hard skills: HTML, CSS

My first web portfolio was created with HTML and CSS, using layout technologies like flexbox and grid. The portfolio is a single page website organized in sections, writing about my passions, web development projects and about me. The webpage has an outer page, called blog, where I add additional information about my projects.

Other projects

Beside Mylifedash, RiderBox and my first website and web-portfolio I had some smaller project where I generally just tried my skills and I took the accent on functionality and performance. They are:

Playgrounschool website - A website which represent a playschool, written with HTML, CSS and a few lines of JavaScript.

Accounting service portfolio - I've tested the ability of writting the website following a ready design from Canva.com. On this project I took the accent on functionality and performance, using only HTML and CSS.

Weatherapp - A static website, similar to mylifedash, exept that weatherapp shows only the current weather. Actually that was an earlier version of Mylifedash, on this project I've used HTML, Bootstrap, JavaScript and fetching data from an API and a JSON file.